https://ksbankers.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
About Us
Bank Leaders of Kansas (BLOK)
About Us
Bank Leaders of Kansas (BLOK)
ABA Training
Bank Leaders of Kansas (BLOK)
ABA Training
Bank Leaders of Kansas (BLOK)
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for ksbankers.com. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and SharingWe collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to improve our website, improve customer service, email communication, and to respond to you regarding the reason you contacted the KBA. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over InformationYou may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
SecurityWe take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Sensitive information that is collected (such as credit card data) is encrypted and transmitted using secure processes. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
RegistrationIn order to use this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about the products/services on our site in which you have expressed interest. At your option, you may also provide demographic information (such as gender or age) about yourself, but it is not required.
OrdersWe request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we’ll use this information to contact you.
CookiesWe use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.
SharingWe partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services.
LinksThis web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Updates
Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 785-232-3444 or by e-mail at kbaoffice@ksbankers.com.
(785) 232-3444
610 SW Corporate ViewTopeka, Kansas 66615Contact Us
E-Newsletter
KBA Staff
Job Board
Upcoming Events
Publications
Education
Bank Leaders of Kansas (BLOK)
Bank Leaders of Kansas (BLOK)
PhonePosition TitleBank NameLocationAsset sizeI would like more information on: (check all that apply)
Traditional Credit Life And Disability Protection
Traditional Mortgage Life & Disability Coverage
TERM LIFE INSURANCE
CUSTOMER BENEFIT PLANS
MORTGAGE IMPAIRMENT ERRORS AND OMISSIONS POLICY (MIE&O)
LENDER PLACED HAZARD INSURANCE
FLOOD ZONE DETERMINATIONS
GUARANTEED AUTO PROTECTION (GAP)
Name
First
Last
Email
PhonePosition TitleBank NameLocationAsset sizeI would like more information on:
PhonePosition TitleBank NameLocationApproximate Asset SizeWhich services are you interested in? (Mark all that apply)
Policy preparation and review
Loan and Account documentation review
Assistance with drafting of basic transactional forms and agreements
Advertising and website review
Compliance and HR auditing services
Audit Services
On-site consulting
